# Emmanuel Monday A. Ajibola

Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria

ajibolaemmanuel02@gmail.com

+234 810 3625 873

linkedin.com/in/emmanuel-monday-aajibola-1b6609280

## Summary

I am a Technology Enthusiast with diverse experience in Front-End Web Development, Python Programming, Social Media Management, Data Entry and Graphic Design.

As a web developer I am proficient in HTML, CSS and Basic Python Programming and have written various programs to automate tasks and improve efficiency.

My experience as a Data Entry Clerk has equipped me with the ability to perform Data Entry Tasks with minimal experience to also analyze data.

In addition, my Social Media Management skills has enabled me to develop and create engaging contents (videos and graphics) which helped boost the social media presence of an organization.

Furthermore, my experience as a Graphic Designer has enabled me implement design strategies in a company which brought about an increase in sales by 50%.

My diverse skill set allows me to excel in different aspects and contribute effectively to projects and teams.

### **Experience**

#### 👔 Social Media Manager

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints

Jun 2021 - Jun 2022 (1 year 1 month)

While serving as a Full-Time Missionary, I also served as a Social Media Manager.

- I developed and created engaging contents(videos and graphics) which helped boost the social media presence of the organization.
- I optimized organization's page and fostered community interaction.
- I reported on contents performances.

# Data Entry Clerk

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints

Jan 2023 - Present (11 months)

- Install and operate firewalls, encryption programs, and other security software.
- I perform Data Entry tasks with Microsoft Office Softwares such as Microsoft Excel and Microsoft
- Organize data in a spreadsheet accurately and efficiently.
- · Verify accuracy of data entered into databases.

# Full-Time Missionary

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints

Jan 2021 - Jan 2023 (2 years 1 month)

- I invited others to come unto Christ by helping them receive the restored gospel through faith in Jesus Christ and His Atonement, Repentance, Baptism, Receiving the gift of the Holy Ghost and enduring to the end.
- Trained new missionaries on work ethics and efficiency.

- Developed knowledgeable skills needed for effective teaching and teamwork.
- · Adapted to different cultures, and traditions and connected with the local people through strong relationship.

#### **Graphic Designer**

Kamark Technologies, LLC

Jan 2023 - Jul 2023 (7 months)

- Implemented good planning and organization skills that helped perform tasks faster.
- Managed company's website and social media pages and also provided IT support which fostered more efficient and profitable operations.
- Job crafted by developing pragmatic marketing skills to convince customers to purchase products.

#### **Graphic Designer**

Mandrs Ventures

Nov 2020 - Nov 2021 (1 year 1 month)

- Implemented design strategies while collaborating and communicating effectively with colleagues, which brought about increase in sales by 50%.
- Managed time wisely by prioritizing tasks effectively which hastened delivery process.
- · Built good customer relations.

#### **Education**



#### BYU-Pathway Worldwide

Pathway Connect, Life Skills | Professional Skills | University Skills | Introduction To **Programming** 

Jan 2023 - Oct 2023

Relevant coursework in Time Management, and Quantitative Reasoning.

Relevant coursework in Microsoft Excel Spreadsheet.

Relevant coursework in Basic Python Programming.

#### SQI College Of ICT

Certificate Of Web Development - Professional Certificate, Computer Software Engineering

Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

I'll study relevant coursework to be a certified full-stack developer, an expert in both the frontend and backend.

I'll be proficient in both frontend and backend languages and frameworks, as well as in server, network and hosting environments.

#### Skills

Organization Skills • Problem Solving • Python (Programming Language) • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Data Entry • Teamwork • Time Management • Communication • Leadership